searchindia.com 2012-11-19

# SearchIndia.com - Search Engine on India

This privacy policy indicates how **Rekha Inc.** uses the information it collects from customers and people/organizations making listing submission or providing services to its network of web sites. **Rekha Inc.** collects details like name, address, e-mail address & phone number etc when a web site is submitted to its network of web sites, when you send us an e-mail, add a comment to our [blog](http://www.searchindia.com/) or interact with us in any other way. **Rekha Inc.** does not rent, sell or share the information it collects **EXCEPT** under the following circumstances:
* Information will be shared with trusted partners who work on behalf or with **Rekha Inc.** under confidentiality agreements.
* **Rekha Inc.** will share the information while responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
*  **Rekha Inc.** believes that it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of **Rekha Inc's** terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in our network in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We will transfer your information if 

**Rekha Inc.** is acquired by or merged with another company. ** _Changes to this Privacy Policy_** **Rekha Inc.** may make changes or update this privacy policy at any time without notice. Please check the privacy policy at periodical intervals to learn about the changes.
